Shaikh M D Rehan Jilan

Address: BTM Layout 1st Stage, Bangalore, Karnataka-560029

E-mail ID: shaikh.jilan06091992@gmail.com

Mobile No: **8197451760**

OBJECTIVE

Analytical and meticulous sales professional with comprehensive experience in relationship-building, partnership cultivation and profit channel growth. Self-motivated leader with natural talent for networking and territory development. Excels at leveraging customer data to deliver strong solutions.

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

WORK EXPERIENCE @ AXIS Bank Ltd as Corporate Sales Manager from May 2020 to Till Date

Coached employees in successful selling methods and encouraged cross-

	selling to drive revenue.
	 Monitored customer buying trends, market conditions and competitor actions to adjust strategies and achieve sales goals.
	Organized promotional events and interacted with community to increase sales volume.
	Developed strategic relationships with key suppliers and clients to foster profitable business initiatives.
Roles, Responsibilities and Achievements	Grew retail sales volume in assigned territory 120% through strategic budgeting and product promotion.
	Handled customer relations issues, enabling quick resolution and client satisfaction.
	Identified, hired and trained highly-qualified staff by teaching best practices, procedures and sales strategies.
	Delivered engaging sales presentations to new clients, explaining technical information in simplified language to promote features and increase client base.
	Worksite Activities on Loans, Insurance.
	KSRTC NTB Acquisition.
	7 New corporates on boarding has been done successfully.

WORK EXPERIENCE @ CITI Bank as Sr. Corporate Associate (B2B Sales) from August 2018 to March 2020

New corporate Acquisition, revivals, NTB

	The state of the s
	Delivering on Card Acquisition/PL targets through Direct Sales and Sell of other banking products such as Mortgage, Banking accounts and third- party products such as Insurance
	. , ,
	Ability to recognize Business potential for acquiring new customers in the
	corporate space and formulate acquisition initiatives.
Roles, Responsibilities	Developed innovative marketing campaigns to increase engagement with
and Achievements	target demographic and drive brand exposure.
	Organized promotional events and interacted with community to
	increase sales volume.
	5 New corporates on boarding had been done successfully.
	Successfully opened 100 accounts in 3 days.

WORK EXPERIENCE @ ICICI Securities as Sr. Manager Corporate (B2B Sales) from November 2017 to August 2018

	Prepared merchandise for sales floor by pricing or tagging.
	Grew sales and boosted profits, applying proactive management strategies and enhancing sales training.
	Maintained records related to sales, returns and inventory availability.
Roles, Responsibilities and Achievements	Increased sales by offering advice on purchases and promoting additional products.
	Educated associates on market trends and stayed up-to-date on forecasts.
	PEHAL: Investment plans Systematic Equity Plans (SEP).
	ICFL: Financial learning Program.
	Customer base of 150 for investment in 6 months.

WORK EXPERIENCE @ Bharti Airtel as a Executive from August 2016 to October 2017

	Customer query handling and providing proper services	
	Planning sales target to individuals	
	Preparing day to day sourcing (data)	
	B2B Sales Corporate connections	
	Project: "A Study on Airtel Payments bank at Rural market and urban market	
	Opened 500 account in month with zero percent of escalation.	
Roles, Responsibilities	Directed staff and managed annual capital budget.	
and Achievements	Researched, proposed and implemented vendor agreements to decrease costs and improve services.	
	Evaluated expenses and set appropriate budget levels.	
	Interacted well with customers to build connections and nurture relationships.	
	Opened 500 account in month with zero percent of escalation.	
	"A Study on Airtel Payments bank at Rural market and urban market	

EDUCATION

Examination	Board/University	Year of Passing
Masters of Business Administration (M.B.A)	Visvesvaraya Technological University, Karnataka.	2016
Bachelor of Business Management (B.B.M)	Vijayanagara Shri krishana devaraya university, Karnataka.	2013
PUC	Department of Pre-University Education, Karnataka	2010
SSLC	Karnataka Secondary Education Examination Board, Karnataka	2008

SKILLS

- > Staff Management
- Business development and planning
- > Sales presentations
- Relationship building
- Marketing strategy
- Sales Reporting
- Sales processes
- ➤ B 2 B sales
- > Analytical problem solver
- New Business Development

CERTIFICATIONS

- > Certified "Own Retail Training Programme" from Centum Learning.
- > Certified (IRDAI) Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India for Corporate Agents.
- ➤ KYC, AML

PROJECT

- MBA Project: A Study on Customer Expectations VS Customer Perception by Service Quality Model At Nirmal Bang Financial Services Pvt Ltd.
- > BBM final year project: "Brand image at Tata motors (Bhagyodaya motors) pvt ltd"
- Mini projects: Customer satisfaction at Hyundai (hottur) pvt ltd"

PERSONAL PROFILE

Name :SHAIKH MD REHAN JILAN

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married

Date of Birth : 06/09/1992

Languages : English, Hindi, Kannada, Telugu

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the above-mentioned details are true to the best of my Knowledge. I am also Confident of my ability to work in a team.

SHAIKH M D REHAN JILAN

Date:

Place: